<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ivan Rimola</title>
    <link>https://rimivan.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ivan Rimola</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://rimivan.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://rimivan.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rimivan.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Erlich administers the Hacker Hostel, a tech incubator where Richard, Big Head, Dinesh, and Gilfoyle live and work in exchange for 10 percent of their potential businesses. Erlich clings to his glory days, when he sold aviation start-up Aviato, a move that, at least in his mind, qualifies him to be a svengali lording over other tech nerds. He still drives a car emblazoned with multiple Aviato logos and smokes copious amounts of weed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gavin Belson</title>
      <link>https://rimivan.github.io/blog/first/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 15:59:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rimivan.github.io/blog/first/</guid>
      <description>Note: This article originally appeared in CodeRag.
Gavin Belson’s name has long been synonymous with innovation—but beyond his work at Hooli, do we even know the man behind the rampant success? In a Code/Rag exclusive, Belson revealed to us 10 things about himself that aren’t common knowledge.
 He’s a nature fanatic! “It’s important to me that Hooli has an effective recycling program, and a personal passion of mine is donating to elephant sanctuaries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://rimivan.github.io/mypage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rimivan.github.io/mypage/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://rimivan.github.io/posts/ir/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rimivan.github.io/posts/ir/</guid>
      <description>PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO PIPPO</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>